https://bengurbryan.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
At Bengur Bryan & Co., Inc., we are committed to safeguarding your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy and how we protect the personal information that we collect from individuals who apply for and obtain our services. The provisions of this notice will apply to former customers as well as current customers.
Information we collect about you:
We collect personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms (such as your name, address, social security number, assets and income), and
Information about your transactions with us or others.
Information we may disclose:
We do not disclose any personal information about you to anyone, except as permitted by law. For example, we may disclose information to cooperate with regulatory and law enforcement authorities or as necessary to protect our rights and property.
Confidentiality and security of your personal information:
We have and maintain strict policies and procedures to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. We restrict access to your personal information to those individuals who have a business need to know that information to provide our services to you. In addition, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.
This policy notice is required by the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA). For additional information contact:
Charles A. Bryan
443-573-3033
cbryan@bengurbryan.com
